本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
整整三十年的心血终于有了回报
Thirty long years and it's all led up to this.
我最伟大的成就
My greatest achievement!
可能应该穿条长裤
Probably should have worn pants.
好刺激  我喜欢
Feisty, I like it.
自 动 扫 描 |
如果我最终成功了
If I finally pull this off,
一切付出就都值得了
it will all have been worth it.
我需要保持冷静低调
I just need to keep playing it cool.
如果有任何人发现了这个
If anyone ever finds out about this...
没关系  我都已经走到了这一步
Yeah, right. I've come this far.
谁又能抓住我呢
Who could possibly catch me now?
快看那里  又来了
See there, there it is again.
我们已经三十年没看到过这样的读数了
We haven't seen readings like this for 30 years.
搜索…
信号是从外太空来的吗
Is it coming from deep space?
是敌人的武器基地吗
An enemy weapons site?
如我所料
Just as I suspected.
先生们  我们去重力泉
Gentlemen, we're going to Gravity Falls.
俄勒冈州
重力泉
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： Peace  挽碧离朱  阿拱
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第一集
Gravity Falls  S02E01  Scary-oke
哦  对
Oh, right.
表演时间到
Show time.
欢迎来到神秘小屋盛大重新开张典礼
Welcome to the grand re-opening of the Mystery Shack!
神秘小屋
Mystery Shack!
我们在此共同庆祝击败小臭鼬吉迪恩
We're here to celebrate the defeat of that skunk little Gideon.
拜托  拜托  嘘声再响亮一些
Please, please, boo harder.
但我不是一个人打倒那个小肥仔的
But I didn't catch that pork chop all alone.
这两位小骗子也有一些功劳
These two scams deserve some of the glory.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
大部分功劳
Most of the glory.
对着镜头笑一笑
Smile for the camera.
你的相机就是块煤渣砖  托比
Your camera's a cinder block, Toby.
我只是想参与其中
I just want to be a part of things.
对着真的镜头笑一笑
Smile for a real camera.
大家一起喊 “傻东西”
Everyone say "Something stupid."
傻东西
Something stupid!
大家别忘了来参加今晚八点的余兴派对
And don't forget to come to the after party tonight at 8:00.
各位  我们将举行幸运卡拉OK
We're doing a karaoke bonanza, people.
灯光  音乐
Lights! Music!
魔法  噗呼
Enchantment! Phoo!
以及由我们家庭乐队
And an amazing
带来的超赞卡拉OK表演
karaoke performance by our family band,
爱的巡逻队阿尔法
Love Patrol Alpha.
噢  我不知道合不合适
Oh, I don't know about that.
我绝不会同意参演
I would never agree to that ever.
太迟了  我已经把你们的名字写在宣传单上了
Too late, I wrote your names on the list.
表演已成定局
It's happening.
各位  记得买票
Buy your ticket, people.
你们的生活中也不会发生其他盛事了
You know you don't have anything else going on in your lives.
说的就是你  比萨小哥
I'm talking to you, pizza guy.
不要失约哦
Don't lame out on me.
哈  整个小镇都爱我们
Ha! The town loves us.
我们终于去除了地毯上吉迪恩留下的臭味
We finally got that Gideon smell out of the carpet.
一切都回到了正轨上
Everything is finally going my way.
嘿  斯坦叔公  现在我们有些空闲时间
Hey, Grunkle Stan, now that we have a moment,
我一直想问你要回我的日志
I've been meaning to ask you for my journal back.
什么  日志
What? Journal?
噢  你指这个旧东西
Oh, you mean this old thing?
它无聊到我根本读不下去
It was so boring I couldn't even finish it.
你什么都没看见
You didn't see nothing.
等等  你就准备把它还给我了
Wait, you're just gonna give it to me?
就这么简单
Just like that?
你还想要啥  亲亲脸蛋
What else do you want? A kiss on the cheek?
我  我要走了
I-- I got to go.
我不介意亲亲脸蛋
I wouldn't mind a kiss on the cheek.
别乱想了
Not gonna happen.
梅宝  我们得谈谈
Mabel, we've got to talk.
我差点失去日志这件事让我意识到
Almost losing my journal made me realize
暑假已经过去一半了
that I'm halfway through the summer
我还是没有搞清楚重力泉的大秘密
and still no closer to figuring out the big mysteries of Gravity Falls.
吉迪恩差点毁了这座小镇
Gideon almost destroyed
就为得到这本日志
the town to get his hands on this journal.
但为什么呢  它是谁写的
But why? Who wrote it?
其他几本日志又在哪里
Where are all the other journals?
当比尔说一切都将改变的时候
What was Bill talking about
这又是意味着什么
when he said everything was going to change?
有重大事件就在我们眼皮底下发生
There's something huge going on right under our noses.
我们是时候不再胡闹而是将此事查个水落石出了
And it's time we stop goofing around and get to the bottom of it.
老弟  你看这笔记本的次数都快数不清了
Bro, you've looked at that thing, like, a bazillion times.
已经没有什么可以被发现的新东西了
There's nothing left to discover.
一半的书页是空白的  你还记得吗
Half the pages are blank, remember?
我只是觉得我离拼出事件真相
I just feel like I'm one
只差最后一块拼图了
puzzle piece away from figuring out everything.
别担心  迪普
Don't worry, Dipper.
神秘火腿王正在调查此事
Lord Mystery Ham is on the case.
我按照自己的规则办事  咋样  咋样
"I play by me own rules! What? What?"
我不知道我怎么会告诉你这件事
I don't know why I tell you things.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
免费停车
嘿  派恩斯先生  我在看到
Hey, Mr. Pines, what's that code word
政府车辆的时候应该喊哪句代号
I'm supposed to yell when I see a government vehicle?
等等  什么  政府车辆
Wait, what? Government vehicle?
美国政府
美国豁免  政府事务
敢按喇叭就逮捕你
神秘小屋已经关门了  所有人都出去
The Mystery Shack is now closed. Everybody out!
我用水管赶走老人时
I will not hesitate to use the hose
可绝不手软
on the elderly.
斯坦叔公  发生什么了
Uncle Stan, what's happening?
对啊  你从来不会关闭礼品店的
Yeah, you never shut down the gift shop.
欢迎光临神秘小屋  先生们
Welcome to the Mystery Shack, gentlemen.
你们有什么需要的吗  钥匙圈
What can I get you? Key chains?
雪花水晶球
Snow globes?
还是这些稀有的美国总统照片
These rare photos of American Presidents?
我是鲍尔斯特工
My name is Agent Powers.
这位是特瑞格特工
This is Agent Trigger.
我们是来调查
We're here to investigate
有关这座小镇上神秘活动的报告
reports of mysterious activity in this town.
活动
Activity.
神秘小屋里的神秘事件
Mysterious activity in the Mystery Shack?
你肯定是在开玩笑
You got to be joking.
我向你保证我并没有
I assure you I am not.
我生来就因为一种罕见的生理障碍
I was born with a rare disorder that makes me
而无法领会到幽默
physically incapable of experiencing humor.
我无法理解你用嘴发出这声音的含义
I don't understand that sound you're making with your mouth.
如果你能配合我们
Now if you'll excuse us,
我们在进行一项调查
we're conducting an investigation.
调查
Investigation.
等等  等等
Wait, wait.
你们刚刚是说你们在调查这个小镇的神秘事件吗
Did you guys say you're investigating the mysteries of this town?
这个消息是机密
That information is classified.
但是  是的
But, yes.
听着  这是我们之间的秘密
Look, between you and me,
我觉得有一种超自然起源的阴谋
I believe there is a conspiracy of paranormal origin
与这座小镇有关联
all connected to this town.
我们离揭开整件神秘事件的面纱
We're just one small lead away from blowing
只差一小步了
the lid off this entire mystery.
你在跟我开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
我正在调查一模一样的事情
I'm investigating the exact same thing.
我在树林里找到了一本笔记本
I found this journal in
里面几乎包含了所有的答案
the woods which has almost all the answers.
如果我们合作  我们可以破解这个案子
If we work together, we could crack the case.
如果你真的有关于这些事件的证据
If you have evidence of these claims,
我们应该谈谈
we should talk.
我们现在就能谈  快  快  快请进
We can talk right now. Please, please, come in.
我有好多东西要给你看
I have so much to show you.
不好意思  特工
I'm sorry, agents.
小孩子总有过于活跃的想象力  以及
Kid has an overactive imagination and, like,
容易出汗的问题
a sweating problem.
说得好
Zing!
什么超自然小镇啦
Paranormal town stuff,
这只是礼品店编的传说罢了
it's just part of gift shop lore.
为了卖出更多的票  你懂的
Sells more tickets, you know.
真有范儿
Swag.
我们还有其他地方要调查
We have other spots to investigate.
我们该走了
We'll be on our way.
我把这些当做证据没收了
I'm confiscating this for evidence.
真是明智之举
Smart move.
等等  不  等等
Wait! No, wait!
我们有很多值得讨论的啊
We have so much to talk about.
够了  孩子
Hold it, kiddo.
相信我  你最不希望出现在
Trust me, the last thing you want around here
派对上的人就是警察了
in a party is cops.
我要没收这张名片
I'm confiscating that card.
你怎么就不能当个正常点的小孩呢
And how's about you go be a normal kid?
和姑娘调调情  或者在窗台上偷个馅饼什么的
Flirt with a girl, or steal a pie off a windowsill.
违禁品
但是  斯坦叔公  你不明白
But, Grunkle Stan, you don't understand.
不准再和那些特工说话了
And don't go talking to those agents.
本来可以成为一次重大突破的
That could have been my big break.
老弟  斯坦叔公也许是对的
Bro, maybe Grunkle Stan is right.
我们今晚要办派对
We're throwing a party tonight.
你今晚就不能暂停一下调查
Can't you go one night without searching
外星人或者复活死者之类的事吗
for aliens or raising the dead or whatever?
我不会复活死者的
I'm not gonna raise the dead.
我只是需要一个给那些特工看日志的机会
I just need a chance to show those agents my book.
相信我  迪普
Trust me, Dipper.
你今晚需要的书只有这一本
The only book you'll need tonight is right here.
我说卡拉  你说OK  卡拉
I say "Kara," You say "Oke." Kara...
卡拉  卡拉
Kara... Kara...
我可以这样玩一整天
I could do this all day.
好的  彩纸炮状态良好
Well, the confetti cannon works.
而且卡拉OK机器里歌曲应有尽有
And the karaoke machine has all the best songs.
《我们建造摇滚村庄》
"We built this township on rock and roll."
《从危机小巷到星光大道》
"Danger lane to highway town."
安帕・桑德拉的《主宰午夜》
"Taking over midnight" By AmperSandra.
孩子们  听着  你们不会想听我这破锣嗓子唱歌的
Listen, kid, you do not want to hear this voice singing.
相信我
Trust me.
斯坦叔公  卡拉OK的重点不在于唱得好听
Grunkle Stan, karaoke isn't about sounding good.
而在于唱得难听  但是是一起难听
It's about sounding terrible, together.
快看啊  这些紫外光弄得我的牙齿很吓人
Check it out! These black lights make my teeth look scary.
恐怖OK
就像我嘴巴里有犯罪现场一样
It's like a crime scene in my mouth.
来吧  你肯定会喜欢的
Come on, you'll love it.
这不公平
It's not fair.
我终于遇见了能帮我解决
Finally I meet someone who can help me
这个小镇谜题的人  斯坦却把他们的名片没收了
solve the mysteries of this town and Stan confiscates their card.
哥们儿  我可能不该告诉你
Dude, I probably shouldn't be telling you this,
但我很确定斯坦把所有东西
but I'm pretty sure Stan hides like
都藏在他房间里
everything in his room.
如果我进斯坦房间  我就惹上大麻烦了
If I go into Stan's room, I could get in so much trouble.
有可能吧
Yeah, you're probably right.
但是这样才刺激啊  笨蛋
That's what makes it fun, dummy.
我迫不及待地要把这些斯坦糖罐给击碎了
Man, I can't wait to smash these Stanatas.
击碎
Smash!
格兰达来参加派对了
Grenda has entered the party!
斯坦的大脑看上好吃极了
Stan's brains look delicious.
闺蜜们
Girls!
我的天啊  我的天啊  梅宝
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh, Mabel!
那是个音响毛衣吗
Is that a boom box sweater?
眼见为实
See for yourself.
戳
Poke!
耶  耶  一起来  耶
Yeah, yeah! Work it! Ah!
我还以为这是个狂欢聚会呢
I thought this was gonna be a rave.
汤普森  快把你的上衣脱掉狂欢起来
Thompson, take off your shirt and make it a rave.
你说什么我都照做
I'll do anything for your approval.
噢  别这样
Oh, come on.
我保证不会发给别人的
I promise I won't send it to anyone.
发给所有人
谁有一只好眼睛和一个好馅饼
Who's got one good eye and one good pie?
这些桶里都是肉
These kegs are full of meat.
谭布丽刚发给我一张超搞笑的图片
Tambry sends me the craziest text.
整个镇子的人都来了
The whole town is showing up
也没见到讨厌的特工们的身影
and no sign of those pesky agents.
温蒂  迪普  那些海报弄得怎么样了
Wendy, Dipper, how are those posters coming along?
斯坦的房间  未成年人禁止入内  说的就是你
我会帮你望风的
I'll keep an eye out for Stan.
你去翻翻他的诡异老头收藏吧
You go rustle through his weird old man biz.
好吧  斯坦叔公  你把那张名片藏到哪里去了呢
All right, Grunkle Stan, where did you hide that card?
没有
Nothing.
我就假装什么也没看到吧
Pretending I never saw that.
等等
Wait a minute.
违禁品
在这儿
Yes!
找到啦
I got it!
鲍尔斯特工
Agent Powers.
嗨  我是迪普
Hi, this is Dipper.
神秘小屋的那个小孩  那个  呃
The kid from the Mystery Shack, the one with the,
有出汗问题的那个
um, sweating problem.
我手里有那本要给你们看的日志
I have that journal I wanted to show you.
你确定你的日志会对我们的调查有帮助吗
And you're certain this journal will help our case?
我百分百确定
I'm 100% positive.
很好  我们这就赶过来
Very well. We're on our way.
对不起  迪普
Sorry, Dipper.
我被彩信转移了注意力
I got distracted.
孩子  你为什么要打那些特工电话
Kid, why did you call those agents?
我早就告诉过你  我告诉过你几百次了
I've told you once, I've told you 100 times,
重力泉根本就没什么超自然的东西
there's nothing supernatural going on in Gravity Falls.
这里的确有
Yes, there is.
都发生了这么多事了  我以为你应该知道了
After everything that's happened, you have to know that by now.
我只知道你这愚蠢的超自然癖好
All I know is that your dumb obsession
总有一天会给我们大家都惹来麻烦
is gonna get us all in trouble one of these days.
现在赶紧去参加派对  抓紧享受
Now go enjoy the rest of the party,
因为派对结束以后  你就被禁足了
'cause when it's over, you're grounded.
嗨  男孩们  很帅哟
Hey, boys, looking good!
格尼  你打扮得不错嘛
Gorney, you clean up nice.
普切克先生  疯狂双腿舞起来
Mr. Poolcheck, move those crazy legs.
你  你这个泳池怪人
You-- You weird pool man.
警官们  有什么问题吗
What's the problem, officers?
我兴奋的心跳超速了吗
Did you catch my face going 90 smiles per hour?
我们接到了有关全镇最吵派对的投诉
We've got complaints about the loudest party in town.
三个字
Three words.
带上我
We want in.
欢迎光临你们的派对之梦
Welcome to your dreams.
同志们  真高兴看到你们
Guys, I'm so glad to see you.
我们合作  就能解开
Working together, we can crack
重力泉所有的大谜题
all the big questions of Gravity Falls.
相信我  这本书就是你们一直在找寻的线索
Trust me, this book is the lead you've been looking for.
我觉得可能需要全面调查
I'm thinking full-scale investigation.
法医啊  研究员啊
Forensics, researchers.
你们有没有直升机呢
Do you guys have a helicopter?
不好意思  应该是  你们有几架直升机呢
I'm sorry, "Helicopters."
孩子  我们真的想相信你  但这看上去就像
Kid, I'd love to believe you, but this just looks like
你叔叔的礼物店里的杂物
more junk from your uncle's gift shop.
看看 “独角绿矮妖”
I mean, "Leprecorn"?
即使我没有幽默神经  我也知道这一点也不好笑
I can't be the only one that thinks that it's not funny.
我能证实  一点也不好笑
I can confirm. Not funny.
不  这是真的  我发誓
No, it's real, I swear.
你应该“送到实验室研究”
You should "Send it to the lab."
是这么说的吗
Am I saying that right?
你叔叔说的想象力过分活跃是真的
Your uncle was right about that overactive imagination.
我们还有文件要写  小孩
We've got paperwork to do, kid.
无聊的文件
Boring paperwork.
等等  这本书是真的
Wait! This book is real.
地精  被诅咒的物品  还有魔咒
Gnomes, cursed objects, spells!
听着  呃
Listen! Uh...
呃  躯体复活
Uh... Corpus Levitas!
呃  恶魔领主  呃  征服世界
Uh, Diablo Dominus! Um, Mondo Vicium!
哈  一只僵尸  如假包换  看见没
Ha, a zombie! A real actual zombie, see.
幽灵日志  比真金还真
Spooky journal, 100% real.
现在我们能合作了吗
Now can we work together?
我的老天爷啊
Mother of all that is holy.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
一只僵尸而已
It's just one zombie.
相信我  这种东西我不知见过多少了
Trust me, I see stuff like this all the time.
幸好只有这么一只
Good thing it was just that one.
我的神啊  你们有办法解决  对吧
Oh, my gosh. You guys can help, right?
小子  我们追查非正常现象已经好几年了
Kid, we've been chasing the paranormal for years,
但从没见过这么夸张的状况
but we've never seen anything like this before.
趴下
Get down!
我的神啊  我都干了什么
Oh, my gosh. What have I done?
蠢货们最近如何  我们是无敌组合
What up, fools? It's Blubs and Durls?
吸金如斗  到处泡妞
Making all that money and getting them girls?
大家觉得怎么样啊  是不是史上最棒的派对
What do you say, guys? Is this party legendary?
我说梅宝  你们说派恩斯
When I say Mabel, you say Pines.
梅宝
Mabel!
我们都要死了
We're all gonna die!
为什么每次别人都不接我的话呢
Why does that never work?
我觉得是地震
I think it's an earthquake.
大家赶紧逃出去
Hey, everybody, we got to get out of here!
我们都完了
We're all doomed.
快点  到我的逃跑背包里来
Quick! Into my getaway pouch!
梅宝  趁现在赶紧逃
Mabel, escape while you still can!
等等  不  别走
Wait! No! Don't leave!
你们还没听我们唱家庭卡拉OK歌
You haven't even done our family karaoke song yet.
迪普  我要求你今晚
Dipper, what's the one thing
不要做什么来着
I asked you not to do tonight?
复活亡灵
Raise the dead.
你做了什么
And what did you do?
复活亡灵
Raise the dead.
站到后面去  兄弟们  局势有点紧张
Get back, dudes. This is about to get intense.
不好意思  等一秒钟
Sorry, one second.
这实在是太酷了  不能否认嘛
You've got to admit this is pretty cool.
僵尸
Zombies!
别恐慌  说不定他们只是扮相很丑的快闪族
Don't panic. Maybe they're just a really ugly flash mob.
同志们  冷静
Dudes, stay calm.
我的一生简直就是在为这一刻做准备
I've been training for this moment my whole life.
看过那么多僵尸恐怖电影
With all the horror movies I've seen,
我绝对知道所有有关
I know literally everything there is to know about
躲避僵尸的策略
how to avoid zombies.
改变主意了  要换换台词
Second thought, gonna flip the script.
我能吃你们的大脑吗
Can I eat your brains?
行还是不行
Yay or nay?
你们的表情像是在说行啊
Seeing some yay faces over here.
快  去高尔夫球车那儿
Quick, the golf cart.
拜托
Oh, come on.
真遗憾
That's a bummer.
不过对我来说是件好事
Good news for me though.
苏斯
Soos!
对不起  伙计  我真的很想吃你们的大脑
Sorry, dude, I just really want those brains.
退后
Stay back!
投降吧  伙计们
Give it up, dudes.
你们的抵抗只会显得我们更酷
Your fighting only makes us look more rad.
我们该怎么办  斯坦叔公在哪儿
What do we do? Where's Grunkle Stan?
他怎么帮忙
How's he supposed to help?
他甚至都不相信超自然现象的存在
He doesn't even believe in the supernatural.
那些特工会毁了一切的
Those agents could ruin everything.
小混蛋
Darn kid!
他不知道自己在搞什么
He has no idea what he's messing with.
他太固执了  是他的缺点
He's stubborn. That's his problem.
我觉得有点像我
Sort of like me, I suppose.
我现在脑子里的事多着呢  没空去担心那几个孩子
I got too much on my mind to worry about those kids right now.
好吧  让我瞧瞧
All right, let's see.
接我一招  傻瓜
Take that, sucker!
没想到这东西还是个好武器
This thing's a surprisingly good weapon.
快  我们得用木板封住所有的窗户
Quick, We need to board up all the windows.
好吧  也许能挡住他们
Okay, maybe that will hold them.
嗨  伙计
Hi, dudes.
顺便说一句  是我教僵尸们怎么弄坏保险丝的
By the way, I taught the zombies how to get to the fuse box.
在这些家伙中我就是个天才
Among these dudes I'm like a genius.
兄弟们  去吃他们的脑袋吧
Get those brains, dog.
迪普  日志中有没有什么
Dipper, isn't there something in the journal
关于打败僵尸的方法
about defeating zombies?
没有  书里没有提到他们的弱点
No! There's nothing in here about weaknesses.
怎么会发生这种事
This can't be happening.
我太想知道答案了  结果却害大家陷入了危险
I wanted answers so bad I put everyone in danger.
现在我们要完蛋了
Now we're toast.
都是我的错  没有人能救我们
It's all my fault and no one can save us.
啊不  梅宝  对不起
No! Mabel, I'm sorry!
迪普
Dipper!
你们俩  快去阁楼  快
You two, attic, now!
叔公  斯坦叔公
Grunkle-- Grunkle Stan?
我说了快去
I said now!
你们这群混蛋活死人
All right, you undead jerks,
准备再死一次吧
you ready to die twice?
唯一可以烦扰我家人的皱皮老怪物只能是我
The only wrinkly monster who harasses my family is me.
看招吧
Take that!
再来
And that!
滚开  无眼怪
Beat it, no-eyes.
谁还想吃我一拳
Anyone else want a piece?
到处都好疼
Everything hurts.
斯坦叔公  真是太不可思议了
Grunkle Stan, that was amazing!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
至少  你不能再否认神秘力量存在了  对吧
Well, at least, you can't deny magic exists anymore, right?
孩子  我早就知道了
Kid, I've always known.
等等  你刚才说什么
Wait. What are you talking about?
我可不是傻瓜  迪普
I'm not an idiot, Dipper.
这个小镇当然很怪诞  而且我知道
Of course, this town is weird and the one thing
怪诞就意味着危险
I know about that weirdness is that it's dangerous.
我一直向你们撒谎隐瞒这些
I've been lying about it to try to keep you away from it,
是为了保护你们
to try to protect you from it.
现在看来谎撒得还不够彻底
It looks like I didn't lie well enough.
我们该怎么办  怎么办
What do we do? What do we do?
按惯例  日志会帮助我们
Normally, the journal would help us,
可关于怎么打败僵尸  书里面什么也没讲
but there's nothing in there about defeating zombies.
没希望了
It's hopeless.
等等  等等  有文字
Wait, wait, wait, the text!
紫外光灯下出现了文字
It's glowing in the black light.
我决定用
隐形墨水躲避
窥探的目光
任何人都可能
在盯着我！
什么
What?
一直以来我还以为自己了解了日志里所有的秘密
All this time I thought I knew all the journal secrets.
原来还有秘密是用隐形墨水写的
But they're written in some kind of invisible ink.
隐形墨水
Invisible ink?
找到了
This is it.
僵尸存在一个弱点
"Zombies have a weakness!
尽管之前人们以为它们不可战胜
Previously thought to be invincible,
可以用完美的三部和声震碎它们的颅骨
their skulls can be shattered by a perfect three part harmony."
三部和声  我们该怎么做呢
Three part harmony? How can we create that?
我天生可以高声尖叫
I have a naturally high pitched scream.
我能用身体发出噪声  有时候是故意这样的
I can make noises with my body. Sometimes intentionally.
男生们
Boys, boys.
我想你们都忘了一个显而易见的办法
I think you're both missing the obvious solution.
嗨  嗨
Hello. Hello.
能听见吗
Does this seem loud?
噢 《绯闻主妇》开始了
Oh, Gossiping Housewives is on.
算了  我已经坐下了
Eh, I already sat down.
僵尸们先生们  我是梅宝
Zombies and gentlemen, I'm Mable,
他俩是迪普和斯坦
they're Dipper and Stan and together,
我们是“爱的巡逻队阿尔法”
we are Love Patrol Alpha!
我可从没同意起那个名字
I never agreed to that name.
开唱吧
Hit it!
午夜狂欢
音乐前奏...
梅宝  我们的命可能不值得这样
Uh, Mabel, our lives may not be worth this.
周五晚上
Friday night
我们要狂欢到天亮
We're gonna party till dawn
爸爸请勿担心
Don't worry, Daddy
我已穿上最爱的舞裙
I've got my favorite dress on
梅宝  这歌词真的很蠢
Mabel, this is stupid.
我们拥进派对
We roll into the party
男生们纷纷看过来
The boys are looking our way
我们跳个不停
We just keep dancing
他们怎么说无所谓
We don't care what they say
男生们团团围在我面前
And all the boys are ganging up in my face
伙计们  我们得一起唱
Guys, we have to sing together
要不然就不管用了
or it won't work.
男生可真无聊
Boys are a bore
快把他们赶跑
Let's show 'em the door
我们占领舞池
We're taking over the dance floor
女孩就要随心所欲
Girls do what we like
今晚是我们的舞台  喔喔
We're taking over tonight, oo-oo
女孩就要随心所欲  喔喔
Girls do what we like, oo-oo
今晚是我们的舞台
We're taking over tonight
我们是迪斯科皇后
We're queens of the disco!
女孩就要随心所欲
Girls do what we like
今晚是我们的舞台
We're taking over tonight
我们的舞台
Taking over tonight
快躲开
Duck!
谢谢你们
Thank you!
今晚我们会与你们同在
We'll be here all night!
搞定你们了  傻瓜僵尸
Deal with it, zombie idiots!
派恩斯  派恩斯
Pines! Pines!
真的很抱歉
I'm sorry about this, guys.
我把一切都搞砸了
I totally ruined everything.
迪普  你在开玩笑吧
Dipper, are you kidding me?
我和这个世界上我最喜爱的两个人
I got to sing karaoke with my two favorite
一起唱了卡拉OK
people in the world.
哪个派对能比这个更过瘾
No party could ever top that.
听着  孩子们  这个小镇古怪得很
Kids, listen, this town is crazy.
所以你们千万要小心
So you need to be careful.
如果你们在我的看护下受了伤
I don't know what I'd do with myself
我实在不知道该怎么办才好
if you got hurt on my watch.
我会让你们拿着那本可怕的日志
I'll let you hold onto that spooky journal
只要你们保证用它
as long as you promise me you'll only use it
只为自保而不是找麻烦
for self-defense and not go looking for trouble.
行  不过你也得向我保证
Okay, as long as you promise me
你没有隐瞒关于这个小镇的
that you don't have any other bombshell secrets
其它让人震惊的秘密
about this town.
我保证
Promise.
我也保证
我们有一堆僵尸造成的破坏要收拾
Man, we have got a lot of zombie damage to clean up.
对了我的员工哪去了
Where's my handyman anyway?
大脑  大脑
Brains! Brains!
我的天啊
Holy Moses!
等一下
Wait!
这有一页讲了如何治好变成僵尸的人
There's a page in here about curing zombification.
需要用大剂量的福尔马林
It's gonna take a lot of formaldehyde.
还有肉桂
Ooh, and cinnamon.
过来苏斯  我们来修好你
Come on, Soos, let's fix you up.
大脑  大脑
Brains! Brains!
苏斯  别闹
Soos, cut it out!
对不起  伙计
Sorry, dude.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
一直以来  作者的秘密
All this time the author's secrets
其实就藏在眼皮底下
were hiding in plain sight.
还有一大堆未解之谜需待探索
A whole new chapter of mysteries to explore.
太疯狂了
That was insane.
我从来没见过那种东西
I've never seen anything like it.
我们向谁报告这件事
Who do we report to?
这简直超乎想象
This is bigger than we imagined.
我们得使出杀手锏了
We need to bring in the big guns.
可是他们不会相信我们的
But they'll never believe us.
那就想法让他们相信我们
Then we'll make them believe us.
这就是我们一直在寻找的小镇
This is the town we've been searching for.
又一个僵尸
Another zombie!
放下武器  放下武器
Drop your weapon! Drop your weapon!
噢  只是个
Oh, okay, it's just--
-那人是谁  -一个非常丑的男人
- Who is that guy? - A very ugly man.